I suspect that lawyers in Thailand do
sospecho que los abogados en Tailandia
not share the defense strategy of
no comparten la estrategia de defensa de
annulling the proceedings,
anulación de los procedimientos
surely neither would
seguramente no la compartiría ni ni
anyone Spanish who is not Garcia
alguien español que no sea García
Montees share it because of the language issue
montees por el asunto de la lengua del
and that is what makes it so
idioma y que eso es lo que hace tan
complicated for the defense in Spain to
complicado para defensa en España
get a qualified defense for
conseguir una defensa cualificada para
Daniel. In Thailand they cannot find a
Daniel en Tailandia no encuentran
lawyer in Thailand who wants to go along with
abogado en Tailandia que quieran seguir
these things and when a lawyer does
los rollos de estos y cuando un abogado
not want to it is because he knows that in other words
no quiere es porque sabe que ponido o
the lawyer does not want to mess around
sea el abogado no quiere mar ronar
by contradicting the prosecution. In
llevándole la contraria a la fiscalía en
that sense, we are going to hire the lawyer who
ese sentido vamos a echar el abogado que
sees fit as long as you pay him.
vea posible mientras que tú le pagues
Come on Javi, here, lawyers
vamos Javi aquí aquí los abogados se
jump on the scent. Here in Spain,
tiran a de huello aquí en España
any lawyer takes your case,
cualquier abogado te coge el caso pum
boom, in the United States, they stop you at
del tirón en Estados Unido te paran en
the doctor's to give you the chance to take it.
el médico para darte para cogerte los
When they don't take it there, you start to
cuando no te lo cogen allí tú empiez a
think about what procedural law there is when
pensar qué derecho procesal habrá cuando
there is no lawyer who, even if you pay him,
hay ningún abogado que ni pagándole
wants to take a case. Of course, of course, start to
quiere caso Claro claro empieza a
think about it and then I would be worried.
pensarlo y ahí yo estaría preocupado yo
As a father, I don't understand Rodolfo, honestly.
como padre a Rodolfo no lo entiendo la